Guide to the Transport Workers Union of America Records WAG.235
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Air Transport Division: Addendum, 1945-1975.
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Cayton Decisions, 1963-1967 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Christensen Decisions, 1968-1974 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Decisions, 1945-1956 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Decisions, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Friedman Decisions, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Hogueland Decisions, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Kennedy and Kelliher Decisions, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Korey Decisions, 1951-1956 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Robertson Decisions, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Stein Decisions (2 binders), 1970-1974 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Thaxter Decisions, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Turkus Decisions, 1965-1970 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Wallen Decisions, 1962-1964 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Wallen Decisions, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Wallen Decisions, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Weisenfeld Decisions, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Wolf Decisions (1 binder), 1971-1974 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - American Airlines System Board of Adjustment: Wolff Decisions, 1955-1957 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - American Airlines Tulsa Board of Adjustment: Quinlan Decisions, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - American Airlines Tulsa Board of Adjustment: Goetz Decisions, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - American Airlines Tulsa Board of Adjustment: Williams Decisions, 1971-1972 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration: Dworkin Decisions, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: Eaton Decisions, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration: Hays Decisions, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration: Horton Decisions, 1969-1971 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Arbitration: Kotin Decisions, 1966-1975 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration: Koven Decisions, 1970-1971 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - National Mediation Board: Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association v. Eastern, United, Seaboard World Airlines, Briefs, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - National Mediation Board: Aircraft Mechanics Fraternal Association v. Eastern, United, Seaboard World Airlines Memorandum, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - National Mediation Board: Airlines Communication Employees Association v. American Airlines, Transcript, Volumes 1-3, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - National Mediation Board: Airlines Communication Employees Association v. American Airlines, Transcript, Volume 4, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board: Airlines Communication Employees Association v. United Airlines, 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines Maintenance and Stores, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Reservoir Technicians (C-1969), 1953 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Stores Dispute (C-2380), Transcript, Volumes 1 and 2, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Stores Dispute (C-2380), Transcript, Volume 3, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Stores Dispute (C-2380), Transcript, Volume 4, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Stores Dispute (C-2380), Transcript, Volume 5, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Technical Foremen (C-2783), 1958 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Technical Foremen (C-2783), Transcript, pp 1-200, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - National Mediation Board: American Airlines, Technical Foremen (C-2783), Transcript, pp 201-411, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - National Mediation Board: KLM Royal Dutch Airlines, Dispute With Employees (C-2098), 1953 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - National Mediation Board: Northwest Airlines Employee Representation Dispute (R-2104), 1953 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - National Mediation Board: Pan American World Airways Agreements (Flight Services and Port Stewards), 1951-1960 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - National Mediation Board: Pan American World Airways at Las Vegas Test Sites, Transcript, Volume 1, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - National Mediation Board: Pan American World Airways at Las Vegas Test Sites, Transcript, Volume 2, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Pan American World Airways: Arbitration, Mechanics and Unskilled Workers, 1946-1947 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Pan American World Airways: Wage Increase, Union Brief, [1947] (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Unprocessed Material: Railroad Division Records, General Files, and Ledgers, 1935-1990
  - National Mediation Board Arbitration Files: Local 2001 - 2318, 1976-1983 (Box 98)
  - Pennsylvania RR: Agreement, 1949-1953 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Penna RR: Agreements, 1949-1953 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Penna RR: Agreements, Nov. 1, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Penna RR: Agreement, Dec. 8, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Penna RR: Agreement (Piece-Work, -Rates) With Pitcairn Steel Car Shop, 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Penna RR: Agreements (General Rules), 1945-1949 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Penna RR: Agreements (Sundays, Holidays), 1945-1949 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Penna RR: Agreements (Rules and Wages), 1946-1949 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Penna RR: Agreement with System Federation #152, 1964-1968 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger, Jan. - Jul. 1964 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger: Anti-Strike Decree, Implementing Agreement (Example), Jan. 30, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Penna-NY General Merger: Clippings, 1961-1966 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger - Correspondence, Jan. - Jun. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger: (Correspondence), Jun. - Dec. 1962 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - PRR-NY Central Merger: Defense and Victory Fund, Mar. - Sept. 1966 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger - ICC Testimony, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: ICC Testimony, Buffalo, NY, Dec. 1962 - Jan. 1963 (Box 99)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: ICC Testimony, Cleveland, OH, Dec. 14, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: ICC Testimony, Columbus, OH, Dec. 17, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: ICC Testimony of Leonard Lecht, Feb. 27, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Penna-New York Central: Implementing Agreement with Employees, 1968-1969 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - RR Division: General Correspondences & National Mediation Board materials & Organizational Drives, 1949-1961 (Box 100)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1947-1953 (Box 101)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1971-1975 (Box 102)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Correspondences, Memorandum, and Meeting Minutes, 1976-1980 (Box 103)
  - CIO Industrial Union Councils, (Representation, Dept of Edu and Research, Policy Committee, and Correspondences), 1951-1954 (Box 104)
  - Railroad Division - Correspondence, Jan. 13, 1971 - Feb. 3, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania RR, 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Checkoff, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Publicity, Mar. - Oct. 1966 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Presidents Council - RR Division, Mar. 23 - Sept. 16 1966 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Milo Shimark, Jan. 3, 1964 - Jan. 29, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1936-1948 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1937-1939 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1948 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1940 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1943 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings and Correspondences, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings and Correspondences, 1941-1942 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings re: Fight for Contract on City Lines, 1941 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings re: Bus Strike, 1941 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1947 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, Correspondences, and Pamphlets, 1945 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings re: Contracts for City Operation and Strike Threat, May - Jun. 1941 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Michael J. Quill Testimony Before the Dies Committee, May 8, 1940 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1941 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Union Cards and Misc., 1953-1966 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1956 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Editorials, Dec. 1957 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, Jul. 1954 - 1955 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, Jun. - Sept. 1955 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Transit Authority (TWU) Publicity, Jan. - Jul. 1954 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, Dec. 1957 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, Dec. 1957 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1947-1949 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings - Flight to Pace NY "Els", 1936-1941 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings - Negotiations and Strike Threat, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Transit Authority Newspaper Clippings, 1935-1939 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Railroad and Airline Agreements and Contracts, 1962-1981 (Box 109)
  - Airriess, Leonard: Reports and Correspondences, 1969-1970 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Alameda Belt Line: Agreements, 1948-1950 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO Railway Employees Division: Agreements, 1950-1954 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO Railway Employeees Division: Agreements, 1960-1966 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe Railway Co., 1954; 1961-1971 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Agreements, 1949, 1951 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Campaign Material, Jul. 11, 1953 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Memorandum of Agreement, Jan. 7, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Proposed Agreements, Undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Supplemental Agreements, Jun. 13, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio RR: Correspondence, Aug. 23, 1949 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe RR: Wage Rates, 1946, 1950 (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Baltimore and Ohio: Checkoff, Jul. - Sept. 1962 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Belen Ice Plant, 1953-1972 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Boyle Ice Company, Feb. 20, 1963 - Mar. 19, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Ciccia, Mike: Reports, May 18 - Nov. 22, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Cornwall Railroad Company, 1947-1962 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1949-1954 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Jan. - Mar. 1955 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Apr. - May. 1955 (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Jun. - Dec. 1955 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Jan. - Nov. 1956 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 27, 1973 - Dec. 4, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Jan. - Jun. 1974 (Box 110, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Jul. - Dec. 1974 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - RLEA & TWU - Audits, Reports, & Correspondences, 1978-1990 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees - Strike, 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Railraod Retirement Board - Correspondences, 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - TWU - Correspondences, Grievances, Contracts, and Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: On-board - Amtrak Shop Ticket & Bad Order Freight Cars-Conrail, 1973-1980 (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - TWU RRD - Reps. Reports, 1966-1971 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1976 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - TWU Newspaper Clippings, 1946-1980 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Misc. - Michael J. Quill - posters, pamphlets, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 15, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 11, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 14, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 13, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 6, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 20 - Feb. 21, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Dec. 21, 1965 - Feb. 1, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. - Feb. 1966 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 31, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 30, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 25 - 26, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 29, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 5, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 4, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Jan. 2, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Strike / M.J. Quill, Jan. - Feb., 1966 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - RLEA - Correspondences, Statements Before Senate, Secretary Reports Vol. II pt. I & 2, Final System Plan Vol. 1 & Vol. 2, Petitions, and Administrative Review, 1974-1980 (Box 113)
  - Amtrak - Railroad Division, Railroad Presidents Council, Railroad Contracts, Correspondences, Case Materials - Appeals, and Misc. Materials, 1961-1974 (Box 114)
  - S.B.A Dockets #56 - 80, J. Hanaberry Misc. Correspondences, Agreements, and Misc. Materials, 1959-1971 (Box 115)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1974 - Dec. 1975 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jan. - Sept. 1976 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Jan. - Jul. 1977 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 5 - Feb. 23, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: RRD Reps, 1974-1977 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Dayton Union Railway Co.: Agreement, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Divco-Wayne Industries, 1963-1967 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Flohr, Bob: Reports, Feb. 28 - Dec. 8, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Flynn, Tom V.: Reports, Jun. 6 - Oct. 7, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Granata, Roy: Reports, Feb. 23, 1969 - Nov. 16, 1969 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Great Northern RR: Agreement, Jul. 1951 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Gulf, Colorado and Santa Fe RR: Correspondence, Mar. 8, 1950 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Hoboken Manufacturers Railroad: Agreement (URRWA, IUMSWA, CIO), Oct. - Nov. 1950 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - International Council: Minutes and Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Indiana Harbor Belt RR: Agreements, 1950-1951 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - John Edgar Thompson FDTN., Undated (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, 1946-1961 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, 1952-1965 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, 1961-1968 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, Mar. 1971 - Apr. 1972 (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Local 1463: Agreements, Undated (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Monessen Southwestern Railway Co.: Agreement (BLFE and BRT), Jan. 24, 1944 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Minutes: Presidents' Council, 1956-1960 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters, 1955-1956 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Brotherhood Railway of Carmen & U.S.: Locals 2001 - 2055, 1977-1980 (Box 117)
  - Minutes: Presidents' Council, 1961-1965 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - New Haven RR: Agreements, 1968-1970 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - New Haven RR: Merger, 1969-1970 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Organizing: General, Feb. - Sept. 1969 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Panhandle and Santa Fe RR: Correspondence, Mar. 8, 1950 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Penn Central: Agreements, 1959-1960 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Penn Central: Agreements, Jul. 13 & 19, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreement, Nov. 24, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreement, Jan. 16, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreement, May 8 - Sept. 2, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreements, Aug. 1970 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreements, Jan. 15 - Dec. 9, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreements, 1972-1974 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Penn Central RR: Agreement, 1972-1973 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Penn Central: Correspondence, Sept. 8, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Penn Central Election, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Penn General Election: Area Reports, Jun. 12 - Oct. 21, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Penn Central RR: Gang Foreman Agreement, Jan. 1 1969 - Feb. 19, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Penn Central/New Haven: Implementing Agreement, Feb. 27 - Mar. 11, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Penn Central: Implementing Agreement with AFL, Jul. 11, 1968 & Jun. 18, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Penn Central Election: Leaflets, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 21)
  - Penn Central RR: Memorandum of Understanding, Oct. 18, 1968 & Nov. 25, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Penn Central RR: Memorandum of Understanding, Feb. 6, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Penn Central RR; New York, New Haven and Hartford RR's: Memorandum of Agreement, 1967-1970 (Box 118, Folder 24)
  - Penn Central: Reorganization, 1973-1977 (Box 118, Folder 25)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board, PA, Santa Fe, St. Louis, So. Pac Co., and Lake Erie RR: Misc Materials, 1947-1970 (Box 119)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger - Letter of Support, May 25 - Aug. 30, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Penn RR: NY General Merger - News Releases and Flyers, Nov. 9, 1961 - Jun. 1, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Penna RR/NY Central Merger: Protection Agreement of Employees ML: Merger, 1962-1975 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger: O'Dwyer and Bernstein, Counsel, Jun. 12 - Jul. 6, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Penna RR: NY Central Merger - Press Releases, Jul. 6 - Oct. 17, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: Publicity, Jul. 9, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Penna-NY Central Merger: Quill-Hoffa Lunch, Jan. 19, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Penna RR: Medical Program, Sept. 30 - Nov. 11, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Penna RR: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Penna RR: Report to the President, Oct. 26, 1955 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Penna RR: Rules Interpretations, Jun. 29, 1949 - Nov. 28, 1949 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Penna RR: Voluntary Relief Dept., Jan. 1, 1949 - Jan. 9, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Penna RR: Wage Agreement, 1964-1965 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - President's Council, May 24 - 28, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Railway Labor Executives' Association (RLEA), 1976-1977 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Rates of Pay: Agreement, 1968-1969 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Retirement, 1974-1976 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Screening Committee: Minutes, Jun. 13, 1972 - Apr. 5, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Shimrak, Milo: Reports, Jan. 6, 1968 - Nov. 15, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Torreaga, Al: Reports, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Travelers Insurance Agreement GA-23000, 1972-1975 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Union Depot Co., 1949-1975 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - United Railroad Workers of America: General Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - United Railroad Workers of America, Local 1463: NY Central RR et al., Sept. 8, 1947 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Railway Ass'n: News, February 26, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Railway Co: Severance Pay Agreement, September 23, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Agreements, Arbitration Awards, and Negotiations, 1960-1964 (Box 121)
  - PR Correspondence, Sept. 28, 1968 - Dec. 12, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Railroad Division, 1962-1964 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - RRD Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Rochester Abandonment, Sept. 18, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - RRD Supplemental Sick Benefit Agreement, 1956, 1975-1976 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Robinson Award - PRR, Jun. 13, 1961 - Feb. 1, 1962 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - RR - Publicity - General, Oct. - Dec. 1961 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - President's Council, Sept. 12, 1961 - Dec. 6, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - E. V. Attreed, V.P. - Director - Correspondences, 1971-1976 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Case Files, Appeals, and Correspondences, 1959-1963 (Box 123)
  - Arbitration: Louis Yagoda Decisions, 1971-1972 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration: Jesse Simons Decisions, 1974-1975 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration: Jesse Simons Decisions, 1972-1973 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration: Jesse Simons Decisions, 1959-1966 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Presidents Council Correspondence, Arbitration Awards, Screening Committee Minutes, Local 2052 & 2044, Amtrak & Conrail Employee Information, 1956-1978 (Box 124)
  - Executive Board: TWU of A: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad, Apr. 9, 1951 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board: TWU of A: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad, Sept. 2, 1960 - Oct. 21, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board: Railroad Division (includes Flyers re 1960 Strike), 1954-1960 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Executive Board: TWU of A: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad, Apr. - Oct. 1955 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board: TWU of A: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1956-1957 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Executive Board: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad - 1960 Strike, Jun. 8 - Sept. 2, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board: Railroad Division - Pennsylvania Railroad - 1960 Strike Legal Papers Enjoining Strike, Sept 8, 1960 - Jan 21, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board: Railroad Division Press Releases: 1960 Strike, Jul 25, 1960 - Sept 1960 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Memorandum of Agreement between Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company, 1962-1965 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - BART Reports: San Francisco, 1969-1973 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Kentucky & Indiana Terminal RR Co., 1952-1962 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Railway Publications and Reports pt. I, 1973-1978 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Railway Publications and Reports pt. II, 1974-1978 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Railway Mediation Agreements & Statements by Arthur D. Lewis, Sept 25, 1964 & Mar 1, 1975 & Aug 6, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Consolidated Rail Corporation Annual Report 1977 (Al Gonrego) (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Testimony - Southern Alleghenies Planning and Development Commission - I.C.C. Hearing on Proposed Rail Abandonment and Rail Center Designation Vol. 1, May 17, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Testimony - Sothern Alleghenies Planning and Development Commission - I.C.C. Hearing on Proposed Rail Abandonment and Rail Center Designation Vol. 2 (Appendix), May 17, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - RRD Welfare Trust, Coal Strike Layoff, TWU Job Description, Severance Pay Dispute, Rail Traffic and Financial Data, 1959-1976 (Box 126)
  - Petty Cash Books, Special Account Receipts & TWU 1977 American Airlines Negotiations, 1937-1955 & 1977 (Box 127)
  - Expedited Handling; Contracting Out of Work; Congress of Railway Unions; Providence & Worcester Co.; Presidents Council Meeting, 1948-1974 (Box 128)
  - Michael J. Quill: Air Transport Division - Local 550 ALSSA, 1962-1963 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Michael J. Quill: Air Transport Division - Local 550 ALSSA, 1961 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Michael J. Quill: Air Transport Division - Local 550 ALSSA: Management Committee Minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 129, Folder 3)